myphotoalbum.com 2010-08-03

# MyPhotoAlbum :: Photo Sharing and Online Photo Album :: Privacy Policy

|  |   
  | 

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

We know that your privacy is very important to you. That's why protecting any personal information, such as your name, address, email address or phone number that you provide to us is of the utmost importance to MyPhotoAlbum. As a result, we have prepared this Privacy and Security Statement to let you know about the manner in which we collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage the personal information you entrust to MyPhotoAlbum or through our authorized service providers ("Service Providers"). When you provide personal information at our Online Stores, our Call Centers, our Sites and to our Service Providers, you are consenting to the manner in which MyPhotoAlbum will collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your personal information, as set out below. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We may collect personal information that you provide us when you: 
    1. Purchase, order, return, exchange or request certain information about our products and services; 
    2. Contact customer service via email or a Call Center 
    3. Visit or register with our Sites or participate in another feature of our Sites, such as a bulletin board; 
    4. Enter into a contest or sweepstakes or respond to one of our surveys; or 
    5. Provide us with comments or suggestions 

**Shopping at MyPhotoAlbum:** If you use a credit or debit card for any of your purchases in our online Store, we will collect your credit or debit card information and keep a history of your purchases. We use this information to process your orders, to ensure proper delivery, to better assist you when you contact or call us as well as to improve our product and service offerings. When you return previously purchased merchandise or request a refund or exchange, you may be asked to give your name, address, phone number. We collect this information to help prevent fraud. 

**Call Centers:** When you call one of our Call Centers about a product, delivery, a billing question or for customer service, you may be asked for information that identifies you along with additional information we need to help us promptly answer your question, such as your name and address and a phone number where we might contact you. We may retain this information to assist you in the future. 

**MyPhotoAlbum Service Registration:** When you register, you are asked for personal information such as your name, e-mail address, and age. Your registration information may be used to make your MyPhotoAlbum experience more personalized. We use this information for verification of identity in event of a lost password and to contact you about our product and service announcements, such as changes in terms and conditions. We also use this information to prevent the abuse of children and comply with Internet registration laws. 

**MyPhotoAlbum Store Registration:** When you register, you are asked for personal information such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, a store password that you. Your registration information may be used to help make your online shopping quicker and easier, by pre-filling certain parts of your shopping information. 

**Contests, Questions or Surveys:** When you ask a question, participate in a survey or enter a contest or sweepstakes, we may collect your name, address, phone number and e-mail address. We use this information to administer your participation in a contest or sweepstakes. 

**Other Uses of Personal Information:** MyPhotoAlbum uses personal information, to continually assess and improve the products and services we offer. We also inform you of products and services, sales and special offers that might benefit you. When you register online for either the store or our service you agree to allow us to contact you via e-mails about our products, services, sales and special offers. 

We may also send you mail, email with information about our product and service offerings if you have provided us with your name and address, email address or phone numbers. If you would like to stop receiving such promotional information from MyPhotoAlbum, please see the Privacy Preferences/Opt-Out section of this Privacy and Security Statement for further instructions on how to register your preferences. 

**Privacy Preferences / Opt-Out:** To update your email addresses for our communications please click on the "My Account" link on the right side of your gallery. To stop receiving any Communications sent by MyPhotoAlbum please click on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email you received. In accordance with the CAN-SPAM law compliance, your opt-out will be honored within 10 business days. Unsubscribing does not apply to communications that are directly related to your registration with MyPhotoAlbum, or the fulfillment of a specific transaction you have requested (for example, a membership status update, or an acknowledgment of a purchase order). Also note, MyPhotoAlbum reserves the right, at a future date, to deny free services (such as a MyPhotoAlbum Library) to any member who has unsubscribed from a MyPhotoAlbum email. 

**Information about Others:** In our Online Stores or on some of the pages on our Sites, you can submit information about other people and compose personalized messages to them. For example, you can share a photo album with friends and family, this sends an email directly to a friend along with a personalized message composed by you. We consider the information you submit and the content of your personalized message to be a private communication between you and the recipient. MyPhotoAlbum will not use or disclose any information you provide about someone else for any purpose other than: 

    1. To send them email containing your personal message 
    2. To identify or resolve technical problems or customer service issues; 
    3. As required by law and to comply with a court order or other legal process; 
    4. To respond to claims that your personalized messages violate the rights of third parties; and 
    5. To protect the rights or property of MyPhotoAlbum and its affiliates. 
  
**Your Suggestions:** We use your feedback, suggestions, survey information and comments solely to monitor and/or improve the use and features of our Online Store, Call Centers, our Sites and our product and service offerings. 

**Children:** Perhaps more important than MyPhotoAlbum's concern for your privacy is our concern for the privacy of children. Due to this, MyPhotoALbum: 

    1. Will never encourage children to use our Sites; and 
    2. Do not allow registration for any of our service to anyone under the age of 13; and 
    3. Attempt to monitor content of our member albums that would violate our Terms; and 
    4. Encourage visitors to report content violations; and 
    5. Never market our products or services to children 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

**Other Service:** To serve you better, we may combine the personal information that you give us on our Sites and in our Store with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our marketing partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize your experience with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes. 

**Companies that work with or on behalf of MyPhotoAlbum:** Some MyPhotoAlbum's operations, such as site advertising or email discount offerings, may be managed by third-party affiliated companies. These companies may have access to your personal information on a confidential basis only to the extent necessary to perform their functions as it relates to providing you with a specific service. At no point will these companies have the right to store your personal identifiable information without your consent.If your purchases are being shipped to you, we will share your shipping information on a confidential basis with our delivery service providers (U.S. Postal Service, Canada Post, or other delivery companies we or you select). Our delivery service providers are prohibited from using your personal information for any purpose other than making the delivery. 

**Sale of Business:** MyPhotoAlbum reserves the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets to a third party acquirer. 

**Legal:** Please note that MyPhotoALbum must provide your personal information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order, or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention of law, or as otherwise required by law. We may also disclose personal information to assist us in collecting a debt owed by you. 

**Access to Personal Information**

You may request access to the personal information that we have about you. As a registered user with our Sites, you can access your profile information at any time by completing the following steps: 

Access to Personal Information from your MyPhotoAlbum Store Account:

    1. Click on the "Login" button at the top of any page in the store, then 
    2. Click on the "My Shop Account" tab in the page header 
  
Access to Personal Information from your MyPhotoAlbum Service Account:  

    1. Click on the "Login" button at the top of any page in your album, then 
    2. Click on the "My Account" link in the page header 
  
For further instructions on accessing the personal information that MyPhotoAlbum may have about you, please see the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy and Security Statement. 

**Additional Information about Our Sites**

**Visiting Our Sites:** In general, you can visit our Sites without telling us who you are or providing us with any information. However, we collect the IP (Internet protocol) addresses of all visitors to our Sites and other related information such as page requests, browser type, operating system and average time spent on our Sites. We use this information to monitor and improve our Sites. 

**Cookies:** Our Sites use a technology called "cookies". A cookie is a tiny element of data that our Sites can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. All pages on our Sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. If you have registered with our Sites, these cookies (1) may let us know who you are, (2) are necessary to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver products and personalized services, and (3) will provide us and our service providers with information that we will use to personalize our Sites in accordance with your preferences. Cookies are also required to optimize your shopping experience in that they allow you to add multiple items to your shopping basket before checking out. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. However, should you decide not to accept cookies from our Sites, you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our Sites. 

**Tracer Tags:** Our Sites may also use a technology called "tracer tags". These may also be referred to as "Clear GIFs" or "Web Beacons". This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on our Sites. These tracer tags are used to help us optimize and tailor our Sites for you and other future website visitors. 

**Third Party Links:** Our Sites may include links to the websites of our business partners, vendors and advertisers. Except as provided herein, we will not provide any of your personal information to these third parties without your prior consent. MyPhotoAlbum provides links to third party websites as a convenience to the user. The inclusion of any link does not imply MyPhotoAlbum's endorsement of any other company, its websites, or its products and/or services. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies, which we recommend you read carefully. We have no control over such websites and therefore have no responsibility or liability for the manner in which the organizations that operate such linked websites may collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal information. 

**Security of Personal Information**

We will maintain the confidentiality of all personal information collected in our Store, our Sites and from our Service Providers and will only disclose such information to employees and Service Providers who require such information for the purposes described in this Privacy and Security Statement. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. 

**Security Measures on Our Sites**

**Secure Shopping:** When you place orders on our Sites, all of your order information, including your card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our Sites from capturing and viewing your personal information. 

MyPhotoAlbum also takes the following measures to protect your personal information online: 

**Passwords** : To provide you with an increased level of security, online access to your personal information is protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. MyPhotoAlbum will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication (including unsolicited correspondence such as letters, phone calls or e-mail messages). Order Information: Since any order information you provide to us on our Sites will be transmitted using a secure connection, if your Web browser cannot support this level of security, you will not be able to order products through our Sites. The most recent versions of Netscape NavigatorTM, FireFox and Microsoft Internet Explorerï¿½ can support a secure connection and can be downloaded for free from the Netscape and Microsoft website respectively. 

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, MyPhotoAlbum cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us on our Sites. 

**Who We Are**

MyPhotoAlbum Inc. a company founded in 1997 and headquartered in New York City. MyPhotoAlbum Inc. is comprised of a family of companies and divisions brought together to provide you with a full suite of photo and online products and services. MyPhotoAlbum Inc. and divisions include: 
    * MyPhotoAlbum
    * MyPhotoPro
    * Go.to

**How To Contact Us**

We want to assure you that MyPhotoAlbum is dedicated to protecting your privacy. 

You can contact us or otherwise communicate your privacy concerns by: 

    * faxing us at 1-212-981-8125 
    * e-mailing us by clicking here
    * accessing your registration information on our Sites 
    * writing us at the address below (please include your e-mail address and phone number with your correspondence along with the information needed to support your request): 

MyPhotoAlbum Attention:   
Privacy Official   
Customer Care  
322 8th Ave, 11th Floor   
New York, NY 10001

**Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement**

To help you track the changes to our Privacy and Security Statement, the date of the material changes to our Privacy and Security Statement will be noted here, **September 26, 2005**. Privacy and Security Statement may be changed at anytime. 

You agree, during the period of this Privacy and Security Statement, that we may: (1) revise the Changes to the Privacy and Security Statement; and any such revision or change will be binding and effective immediately on posting of the revised statement or change to the service(s) on our web site, or on notification to you by e-mail or regular mail. You agree to review our web site, including the Privacy and Security Statement, periodically to be aware of any such revisions. If you do not agree with any revision to the Statement, you may terminate your services at any time by providing us with notice by e-mail or regular mail as per the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy and Security Statement. Notice of your termination will be effective on receipt and processing by us. You agree that, by continuing to use the Services following notice of any revision to this Privacy and Security Statement or change in service(s), you abide by any such revisions or changes 

Copyright © 2020 MyPhotoAlbum. All Rights Reserved. 

|   
|  |
